<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on C2PA</title>
    <link>https://c2pa.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on C2PA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 19:11:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://c2pa.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Joins C2PA Steering Committee</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/openai_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/openai_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; May 07, 2024 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA) announced that OpenAI, a leader in artificial intelligence research and deployment, has joined the C2PA as a steering committee member. This marks a significant milestone for the C2PA and will help advance the coalition’s mission to increase transparency around digital media as AI-generated content becomes more prevalent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google to join C2PA to help increase transparency around digital content</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/google_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:10:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/google_pr/</guid>
      <description>Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA), a global standards body advancing transparency online through certifying the provenance of digital content, announced that Google has joined C2PA as a steering committee member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Official Content Credentials Icon</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/contentcredentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/contentcredentials/</guid>
      <description>Today the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA) is introducing the new and official Content Credentials “icon of transparency,” a mark that will provide creators, marketers and consumers around the world with the ultimate signal of trustworthy digital content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2PA welcomes first advertising holding company to steering committee</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/publicis_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 01:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/publicis_pr/</guid>
      <description>Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity welcomed Publicis Groupe, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading marketing organizations, as the newest steering committee member focused on digital media transparency and global adoption of content provenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Corporation Joins C2PA as Steering Committee Member</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/sony_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 18:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/sony_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; March 16, 2022 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA) has added Sony Corporation (“Sony”) as the latest steering committee member to help provide creators, consumers, and others with opt-in, flexible ways to understand the authenticity and provenance of various media types. The C2PA recently released the world’s first industry-standard specification for content provenance to promote widespread adoption of tools to identify the source and history of digital content. Sony’s membership marks a major addition to the coalition as one of the world’s leading providers of electronics products and solutions for consumer and professional markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2PA Releases Specification of World&#39;s First Industry Standard for Content Provenance</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/release_1_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/release_1_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; January 26, 2022 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity, an organization established to provide publishers, creators, and consumers with opt-in, flexible ways to understand the authenticity and provenance across various media types, released version 1.0 of its technical specification for digital provenance. This specification is the first of its kind and empowers content creators and editors worldwide to create tamper-evident media, by enabling them to selectively disclose information about who created or changed digital content and how it was altered. The C2PA&amp;rsquo;s work is the result of industry-wide collaborations focused on digital media transparency that will accelerate progress toward global adoption of content provenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2PA Releases Draft Spec</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/draft_1_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/draft_1_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; September 1, 2021 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA), a Joint Development Foundation project established to scale trust in online content, released its content provenance specifications – in draft form – for community review and feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Joins C2PA</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/twitter_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/twitter_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; May 13, 2021 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, Twitter joins the cross-industry Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA), a Joint Development Foundation project established to scale trust in online content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2PA Founding Press Release</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/c2pa_initial_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/c2pa_initial_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN JOSE, Calif., and REDMOND, Wash. &amp;mdash; Feb. 22, 2021 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; A group of influential technology and media companies has partnered to form the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA), a Joint Development Foundation project established to address the prevalence of disinformation, misinformation and online content fraud through developing technical standards for certifying the source and history or provenance of media content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
