<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on C2PA</title>
    <link>https://c2pa.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on C2PA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 14:28:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://c2pa.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sony Corporation Joins C2PA as Steering Committee Member</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/sony_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/sony_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; March 16, 2022 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA) has added Sony Corporation (“Sony”) as the latest steering committee member to help provide creators, consumers, and others with opt-in, flexible ways to understand the authenticity and provenance of various media types. The C2PA recently released the world’s first industry-standard specification for content provenance to promote widespread adoption of tools to identify the source and history of digital content. Sony’s membership marks a major addition to the coalition as one of the world’s leading providers of electronics products and solutions for consumer and professional markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2PA Releases Specification of World&#39;s First Industry Standard for Content Provenance</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/release_1_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/release_1_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; January 26, 2022 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity, an organization established to provide publishers, creators, and consumers with opt-in, flexible ways to understand the authenticity and provenance across various media types, released version 1.0 of its technical specification for digital provenance. This specification is the first of its kind and empowers content creators and editors worldwide to create tamper-evident media, by enabling them to selectively disclose information about who created or changed digital content and how it was altered. The C2PA&amp;rsquo;s work is the result of industry-wide collaborations focused on digital media transparency that will accelerate progress toward global adoption of content provenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2PA Releases Draft Spec</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/draft_1_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/draft_1_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; September 1, 2021 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA), a Joint Development Foundation project established to scale trust in online content, released its content provenance specifications – in draft form – for community review and feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Joins C2PA</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/twitter_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/twitter_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Calif. &amp;mdash; May 13, 2021 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; Today, Twitter joins the cross-industry Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA), a Joint Development Foundation project established to scale trust in online content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2PA Founding Press Release</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/post/c2pa_initial_pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/post/c2pa_initial_pr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;SAN JOSE, Calif., and REDMOND, Wash. &amp;mdash; Feb. 22, 2021 &amp;mdash;&lt;/strong&gt; A group of influential technology and media companies has partnered to form the Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA), a Joint Development Foundation project established to address the prevalence of disinformation, misinformation and online content fraud through developing technical standards for certifying the source and history or provenance of media content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/about/about/</guid>
      <description>The Coalition for Content Provenance and Authenticity (C2PA) is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jointdevelopment.org/&#34;&gt;Joint Development Foundation&lt;/a&gt; project that brings together the efforts of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://contentauthenticity.org/&#34;&gt;Content Authenticity Initiative (CAI)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.originproject.info/&#34;&gt;Project Origin&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charter</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/about/charter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/about/charter/</guid>
      <description>With the digital transformation of information sharing, the ability to trace the provenance of media has become critical. To address this issue at scale for publishers, creators and consumers, the Consortium will develop technical specifications for establishing content provenance and authenticity. The specifications will be informed by scenarios, workflows and requirements gathered from industry experts and partner organizations, including the Project Origin Alliance and the Content Authenticity Initiative (CAI.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/about/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/about/resources/</guid>
      <description>A collection of resources for additional reading about the C2PA including whitepapers and videos from the CAI and Project Origin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Content Provenance Event: January 26, 2022</title>
      <link>https://c2pa.org/jan-2022_event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c2pa.org/jan-2022_event/</guid>
      <description>Digital Content Provenance: Possibilities &amp;amp; opportunities for the future of the internet in the deepfake and disinformation era Join us for the release and demonstration of the 1.0 version of the end-to-end open technical standard for certifying the source and history of media content. Policymakers, academics and industry leaders will discuss the future of responsible digital media creation, publication and sharing.
Agenda    Topic Speaker(s)     Welcome and Introduction to the C2PA Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
